Monsters come in many forms.
10 Cloverfield Lane is a thriller, science fiction,
drama film directed by Dan Trachtenberg.
After a catastrophic car crash, a young woman wakes up in a survivalist's underground bunker, where he claims
to have saved her from an apocalyptic attack that has left the outside world uninhabitable.
Howard, played by John Goodman.
Michelle, played by Mary Elizabeth Winstead.
Emmett, played by John Gallagher Jr..
Driver, played by Douglas M. Griffin.
Woman, played by Suzanne Cryer.
Ben (voice), played by Bradley Cooper.
10 Cloverfield Lane is a 2016 American science fiction horror thriller film
directed by Dan Trachtenberg in his directorial debut, produced by J.
Abrams and Lindsey Weber and written by Josh Campbell,
Matthew Stuecken, and Damien Chazelle.
The second film in the Cloverfield franchise, it stars Mary
Elizabeth Winstead, John Goodman, and John Gallagher Jr.
The story follows a young woman who, after a car crash, wakes up in an underground bunker with
two men who insist that an event has left the surface of Earth uninhabitable.
The film was developed from a script titled The Cellar; but under production by Bad
Robot, it was turned into a spiritual successor to the 2008 film Cloverfield.
It is presented in a third-person narrative, in contrast
to its predecessor's found-footage style.
Principal photography took place under the title Valencia in New
Orleans, Louisiana, from October 20 to December 15, 2014.
10 Cloverfield Lane premiered in New York City on March 8, 2016,
and was released in select countries on March 10.
It was released in the United States on March 11, 2016,
in both conventional and IMAX formats.
The film received positive reviews and grossed over $110 million worldwide.
A successor, The Cloverfield Paradox, was released on February 4, 2018.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, paranoia, bunker, basement, survivalist.
The tone is dark and emotional and thought_provoking.